Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration Records UA060
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration Records
1987 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration
UA060
7.45 Linear Feet 7 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Annual reports; Patent files; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Office for Technology and Industry Collaboration was established in 2000 to handle intellectual property issues across all divisions of the university. The office is located on the Boston campus.
The Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration (OTL and IC) is responsible for facilitating the transfer of Tufts technology for public use and benefit. OTL and IC evaluates, obtains proprietary protection for, and assists in the distribution of technology for research and commercial purposes. OTL and IC is responsible for transferring technology for commercial development by identifying potential markets and negotiating license agreements with industry partners, be they large or start-up companies.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains annual reports and patents maintained by the Office of Technology and Industry Collaboration.
Research and Research Administration; Legal and Regulatory
- Annual Reports, 2000; UA060.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains annual reports of the Office for Technology and Industry Collaboration.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Annual report, 2000; UA060.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
- Patent files, 1987 -- 2017; UA060.002; 7.0 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged alphabetically by last name of patent holder, within each accession.
  - Abriola Linda - T001445 - US Patent No. 8,615,379, 2013; UA060.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Alekshun, Michael - T001152 - US Patent No. 7,202,339, 2007; UA060.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Alroy, Joseph - T000992 - US Patent No. 5,141,925, 1992; UA060.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Altman, Greg - T001049 - US Patent Nos. 6,287,340; 6,990,898 B2, 2000 -- 2005; UA060.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000971 - US Patent No. 7,829,530 B2 - Australian Patent Nos. 2,007,202,745; 2,003,264,609, 1999 -- 2010; UA060.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000971 - US Patent Nos. 6,803,357; 7,078,381; 7,459,428; 8,318,669; 8,513,190; 7,157,429 - Australian Patent Nos. 766,219; 2,011,200,657, 1998 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000979 - US Patent No. 6,875,737 B1, 2005; UA060.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000983 - US Patent Nos. 7,230,074 B2; 5,462,928; 6,825,169 B1, 1995 -- 2007; UA060.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000986 - US Patent Nos. 5,580,979 - 5,776,902, 1996 -- 1998; UA060.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001026 - Australian Patent No. 775164, 1999; UA060.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001139 - Japan Patent No. 4771661 - US Patent No. 7727964 B2 - Australia Patent No. 2002357767, 2001 -- 2009; UA060.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001183 - US Patent No. 8,410,053 - Australia Patent No. 2,002,360,453, 2008 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001182 - US Patent No. 7,691,967 B2 - Australia Patent No. 2,003,228,793, 2008 -- 2010; UA060.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001191 - US Patent Nos. 7,259,234; 7,994,121 - Australia Patent No. 2,011,200,062 - Hong Kong Patent No. HK1,088,840, 2004 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001191 - Japan Patent No. 4,699,374 - European Patent No. 1,633,384 - Chinese Patent ZL200,480,019,850.0 - Australian Patent 2,004,240,630, 2003 -- 2012; UA060.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001257 - India Patent No. 246,858 - Mexico Patent No. 284,671, 2005 -- 2011; UA060.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001281 - Taiwan Patent No. I382,836 - Russia Patent No. 2,379,315 - Mexico Patent No. 285,549 - Japan Patent No. 4,781,347 - China Patent No. ZL 200,580,011,588.X - Australia Patent No. 2,005,216,970, 2005 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001282 - US Patent Nos. 7,569,546; 8,124,580 - Japan Patent No. 5,048,486 - Korea Patent No. 10-1,185,609 - Mexico patent No. 276,568 - Australia Patent No. 2,005,275,009, 2004 -- 2012; UA060.002.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001293 - China Patent No. 2,006,800,030,771.9 - Mexico Patent No. 304,239 - US Patent No. 7,998,997 - Australia Patent No. 2,006,264,305, 2005 -- 2012; UA060.002.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001350 - US Patent No. 8,318,668 B2 - Australia Patent No. 2,006,287,562, 2012; UA060.002.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001384 [1 of 3] - US Patent No. 8,268,880 B2, 2012; UA060.002.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001384 [2 of 3] - Mexico Patent No. 312,708, 2006; UA060.002.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001384 [3 of 3] - Israel Patent No. 192,134 - Australia Patent No. 2,006,339,348 - Japan Patent No. 5,270,369 - US Patent Nos. 8,513,187; 8,563,533, 2006 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001396 - Australia Patent No. 2,007,281,212 - US Patent No. 8,377,971 - Japan Patent No. 5,270,545 - China Patent No. ZL200,780,037,196.X - Mexico Patent No. 316,782, 2007 -- 2013; UA060.002.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001674 - US Patent No. 8,450,316, 2013; UA060.002.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001035 - US Patent No. 7,592,503 B2 - European Patent No. 1,127,112, 2007 -- 2009; UA060.002.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Camilli, Andrew - T001482 - US Patent Nos. 8,642,046; 8,219,180, 2014; UA060.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Cao, Caroline - T001490 - US Patent Nos. 8,725,234; 8,219,180, 2012 -- 2014; UA060.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Chikaraishi, Dona - T000954 - US Patent No. 5,591,626, 1997; UA060.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Chudyk, Wayne - T000595 - US Patent No. 4,782,234, 1988; UA060.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Cochran, Brent - T000659 - US Patent No. 6,066,723, 2000; UA060.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - D'Alarcao, Marc - T001286 - Australian Patent No. 2,005,295,472, 2012; UA060.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Dawson, Dean - T001342 - US Patent No. 7,556,929 B2, 2009; UA060.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Degtereu, Alexei - T001634 - US Patent No. 8,628,961, 2014; UA060.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Dodman, Nicholas - T000924 - US Patent No. 5,554,383, 1996; UA060.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Dodman, Nicholas - T000926 - US Patent No. 5,314,888, 1994; UA060.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Dodman, Nicholas - T000929 - US Patent No. 4,692,451, 1987; UA060.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Doumanidis, Charalabos - T000918 - US Patent No. 5,552,575, 1996; UA060.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Fantini, Sergio - T001165 - US Patent No. 7,962,187 B2, 2011; UA060.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Feng, Hanping - T001531 - US Patent No. 8,206,940, 2012; UA060.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Flytzani-Stephanopoulos, Marta - T001330 - European Patent No. 1,819,420 - Australia Patent No. 2,005,304,693 - US Patent No. 7,871,459 B2 - China Patent No. ZL 200,580,046,140.1 - Canada Patent No. 2,628,970, 2011 -- 2014; UA060.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Flytzani-Stephanopoulos, Marta - T001553 - US Patent No. 8,394,736 B2, 2013; UA060.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Goldner, Ronald - T000859 - US Patent No. 6,952,060 B2, 2005; UA060.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Goldner, Ronald - T000870 - US Patent No. 5,532,869, 1996; UA060.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Goldner, Ronald - T000889 - US Patent No. 6,982,132 B1, 2006; UA060.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Greenberg, Andrew - T000852 - US Patent No. 6,897,019 B1, 2005; UA060.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Haydon, Philip - T001697 - US Patent No. 8,598,141 B2, 2013; UA060.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Hassoun, Soha - T001217 - US Patent No. 7,797,647 B2, 2010; UA060.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Herman, Ira - T000839 - US Patent No. 6,521,420 B1, 2003; UA060.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Herman, Ira - T000842 - US Patent No. 5,851,522, 1998; UA060.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Herman, Ira - T000842 - Canada Patent Nos. 2,225,898; 2,178,396 - US Patent No. 5,718, 899, 1998 -- 2012; UA060.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Herman, Ira - T001066 - US Patent No. 6,780,987, 2004; UA060.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Herman, Ira - T001414 - US Patent No. 8,357,655; T001632 - US Patent No. 8,466,106, 2013; UA060.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Hoffman, Andrew - T000836 [1 of 2] - US Patent No. 7,094,206 B2, 2006; UA060.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Hoffman, Andrew - T000836 [2 of 2] - US Patent Nos. 6,287,264 B2; 6,723,055 B2, 2001 -- 2004; UA060.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Huber, Brigitte - T000828 - US Patent No. 6,706, 868 B2, 2004; UA060.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Huber, Brigitte - T000832 - US Patent No. 738,956, 2002; UA060.002.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Huber, Brigitte - T000833 [1 of 2] - US Patent No. 6,692,753 B2 - Greek Patent No. 20,030,404,559 - Europe Pat. No. 0,975,359 B1, 1998 -- 2004; UA060.002.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Huber, Brigitte - T000833 [2 of 2] - European Patent No. 0,975,359, 1998 -- 2004; UA060.002.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Huber, Brigitte - T001075 - US Patent No. 6,689,364, 2004; UA060.002.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [1 of 3] - US Pat. No. 7,959,915 B2 - Japan Pat. No. 4,971,788 - Australia Pat. No. 2,005,221,470, 2010 -- 2012; UA060.002.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [2 of 3] - US Pat. No. 8,529,891 B2 - Romania Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Austria Pat. No. 1,603,941 B1 - Bulgaria Pat. No. 1,603,941 B1, 2011 -- 2013; UA060.002.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [3 of 3] - Cyprus Pat. No. CY1111365 - Denmark Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Estonia Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Europe Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Finland Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Germany Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Greece Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Hungary Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Czech Republic Pat. No. 1,603,941 - India Pat. No. 234,114, 2003 -- 2011; UA060.002.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [1 of 3] - Italy Patent No. 1,603,941, 2011; UA060.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [2 of 3] - Netherlands Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Poland Pat No. 1,603,941 - Portugal Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Romania Pat. No. 1,603,941, 2011; UA060.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 [3 of 3] - Slovakia Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Slovenia Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Spain Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Sweden Pat. No. 1,603,941 - Turkey Pat. No. 1,603,941, 2004 -- 2011; UA060.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001219 - Japan Pat. No. 4,638,735 - Canada Pat. No. 2,525,994, 2010 -- 2012; UA060.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T000820 - US Pat. No. 6,534,294 B1, 2003; UA060.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001219 - US Pat. No. 8,071,722 B2; 7,674,882 B2, 2010 -- 2011; UA060.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001233 - US Pat. Nos. 7,842,780 B2; 8,361,617 B2, 2010 -- 2013; UA060.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001239 - US Pat. No. 7,727,575 B2, 2010; UA060.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001255 - US Pat. Nos. 8,614,293 B2; 7,635,755 B2 - Japan Pat. No. 4,698,596, 2009 -- 2013; UA060.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001274 - US Pat. Nos. 8,530,625; 8,178,656, 2012 -- 2013; UA060.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001336 - US Pat. Nos. 8,501,437 B2; 7,960,509 B2; 8,129,141 B2, 2011 -- 2013; UA060.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001367 - US Patent No. 8,354,501 - European Pat. No. 1,915,436, 2011 -- 2013; UA060.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001463 - Australia Pat. No. 2,008,260,156 - Mexico Pat. No. 309,591 - Russia Pat. No. 019,118 - US Pat. Nos. 8,722,067; 8,187,616, 2008 -- 2014; UA060.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001528 - US Patent No. 8,206,774 B2, 2012; UA060.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001557 - European Pat. No. 2349366 - US Pat. No. 8,501,172 B2, 2013; UA060.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001594 - US Pat. No. 8,293,486 B2, 2012; UA060.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001559 - Mexico Pat. No. 297,675, 2009; UA060.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Kaplan, David - T001601 - US Pat. No. 8,278,498 B2, 2014; UA060.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Kauer, John - T001059 - US Pat. No. 6,649,416 B1, 2003; UA060.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Koza, Darrell - T001047 - US Patent Nos. 7,361,674 B2; 7,094,806 B2; 6,624,168 B2, 2003 -- 2008; UA060.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Kounaves, Samuel - T001204 - US Pat. Nos. 7,632,393 B2; 8,216,447 B2, 2009 -- 2012; UA060.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Kraus, Karl - T000804 - US Pat No. 5,976,133, 1999; UA060.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Kraus, Karl - T000805 - US Pat. Nos. 5,746,741, 1998; UA060.002.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Kumar, Krishna - T001142 - US Pat Nos. 7,371,867 B2; 7,132,559 B2, 2006 -- 2008; UA060.002.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Kumar, Krishna - T001285 - US Pat. No. 7,612,166 B2, 2009; UA060.002.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Kumar-Singh, Rajendra - T001514 - US Pat. No. 8,324,182 B2, 2012; UA060.002.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000782 - US Pat. Nos. 6,136,602; 6,485,973 B2, 2000 -- 2002; UA060.002.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000792 - US Pat. Nos. 5,811,412; 5,589,470; 5,258,372; 5,021,407; 5,064,821; 4,806,529; 6,756,365 B2, 1989 -- 2004; UA060.002.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000779 - US Pat. Nos. 7,202,235 B2; 6,833,365 B2, 2004 -- 2007; UA060.002.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000788 - US Pat. No. 5,650,321, 1997; UA060.002.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000783 - Canada Pat. No. 2,329,120, 2011; UA060.002.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T000792 - Canada Pat. No. 1,225,332, 1987; UA060.002.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Levy, Stuart - T001039 - US Pat. No. 6,677,133, 2004; UA060.002.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Lewis, Kim - T000769 - US Pat. No. 6,875,439 B2, 2005; UA060.002.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Mescas, Joan - T001244 - US Pat. No. 7,281,557 B2, 2008; UA060.002.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Meydan, Simin Nikbin - T000750 - US Pat. No. 6,642,259 B1, 2003; UA060.002.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Mark - T000771 - European Pat. No. 1,661,883, 2010; UA060.002.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Mark - T000778 - Japan Pat. No. 5,027,436 - Europe Pat. No. 1,679,305 - Japan Pat. No. 4,925,549 - Eurasia Pat. No. 013,908, 2010 -- 2012; UA060.002.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Mark - T001041 - Taiwan Pat. No. 08,811,818, 2003; UA060.002.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Mark - T001127 - Japan Pat. No. 5044084 - S. Korea Pat. No. 10-1083571, 2011 -- 2012; UA060.002.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001430 - European Patent No. 2,086,749, 2013; UA060.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001432 - US Patent No. 8,529,835, 2013; UA060.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001435 - US Patent No. 8,195,021, 2012; UA060.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001643 - US Patent No. 8,666,471, 2013; UA060.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001436 - US Patent No. 8,574,461, 2013; UA060.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Overstrom, Eric - T001035 - US Patent No. 6,781,030, 2004; UA060.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Overstrom, Eric - T001212 - US Patent No. 7,612,250, 2009; UA060.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Ordovas, Jose - T001256 - Chinese Patent No. ZL 2004 8 34302.5, 2009; UA060.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Panetta, Karen - T001495 - US Patent No. 8,285,076, 2012; UA060.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Panetta, Karen - T001533 - US Patent No. 8,285,070, 2012; UA060.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Paniliatis, Bruce - T001542 - US Patent No. 8,609,835, 2013; UA060.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Panjwani, Noorjahan - T001149 - US Patent No. 6,976,021, 2005; UA060.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Panjwani, Noorjahan - T001226 - Japan Patent No. 5,146,836 - Mexican Patent No. 304,384 - US Patent No. 7,189,697, 2006 -- 2012; UA060.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Perrin, Mercio - T000724 - US Patent No. 8,114,412, 2012; UA060.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Rennie, Glen - T001041 - US Patent No. 6,617,318 - Eurasian Patent No. 005,118, 2003; UA060.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Rennie, Glen - T001041 - Israeli Patent No. 183,124 - Canadian Patent Nos. 2,672,722; 2,383,364, 2009 -- 2013; UA060.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Robbat, Albert - T000715 - US Patent No. 5,668,373, 1997; UA060.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Shoemaker, Charles - T001452 - US Patent No. 8,349,326, 2013; UA060.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Shoemaker, Charles - T001507 - US Patent No. 8,492,109, 2013; UA060.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Sonenshein, Abraham - T001314 - US Patent Nos. 8,202,695; 8,592,162; 8,592,162, 2012 -- 2013; UA060.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Sonkusale, Sameer - T001440 - US Patent No. 8,159,288, 2012; UA060.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Soto, Ana - T001017 - US Patent No. 6,994,992, 2006; UA060.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Toole, Bryan - T001173 - Japan Pat. No. 5,027,387 - Australian Pat. No. 2,003,280,471 - US Patent Nos. 8,093,217; 8,648,047, 2009 -- 2014; UA060.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Tzipori, Saul - T000652 - US Patent Nos. 7,910,706; 7,910,096; 7,910,095, 2011; UA060.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Valluzzi, Regina - T001216 - US Patent No. 8,580,924, 2013; UA060.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Valluzzi, Regina - T001216 - Indian Patent No. 229091; European Pat. No. 1565203; Japanese Pat. No. 4800622; Australian Pat. Nos. 2009227842; 2003294240 - Canadian Pat. No. 2,504,327 - US Pat. No. 7,572,894, 2009 -- 2013; UA060.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Waldor, Matthew - T001262 - US Patent No. 7,247,437, 2007; UA060.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Waldor, Matthew - T001446 - US Patent No. 8,414,903, 2013; UA060.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000627 - US Patent No. 6,667,159 - European Pat. No. 1060239 - Japanese Pat. No. 3471753, 2003 -- 2004; UA060.002.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000628 - US Patent No. 6,023,540, 2000; UA060.002.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000628 - US Patent No. 7,622,294 - European Pat. No. 0966671 - Canadian Pat. Nos. 2,283,742; 2,343,377, 2008 -- 2011; UA060.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000628 - Australian Pat. Nos. 746365; 773211 - US Pat. No. 6,859,570 - Japanese Pat. No. 3836323, 2002 -- 2006; UA060.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000635 - US Pat. No. 5,512,490, 1996; UA060.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000636 - Canadian Pat. No. 2,128,413 - European Pat. No. 0627074, 2007; UA060.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000645 - US Pat. Nos. 5,114,864; 5,252,494, 1992 -- 1993; UA060.002.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000646 - US Pat. No. 5,633,972, 1997; UA060.002.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000645 - US Pat. Nos. 5,143,853, 1992; UA060.002.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T000645 - US Pat. Nos. 5,254,477; 4,822,746, 1989 -- 1993; UA060.002.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Walt, David - T001027 - US Patent No. 6,285,807, 2001; UA060.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001038 - US Patent No. 7,754,498 - Japan Patent Nos. 4,471,493; 4,550,149; 3,886,161 - European Patent No. 1,021,718, 2006 -- 2010; UA060.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001038 - Australian Patent No. 2,003,200,922 - US Patent Nos. 7,115,884; 7,348,181, 2006 -- 2008; UA060.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001038 - Canadian Patent No. 2,305,545 - US Patent Nos. 8,030,094; 8,426,217, 2006 -- 2013; UA060.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001085 - US Patent No. 7,250,267, 2007; UA060.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001087 - US Patent No. 6,999,657, 2006; UA060.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001130 - US Patent No. 6,720,007, 2004; UA060.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001190 - US Patent No. 6,991,939, 2006; UA060.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001177 - US Patent No. 7,480,433, 2009; UA060.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001296 - US Patent No. 8,663,973, 2014; UA060.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001355 - US Patent No. 7,595,473, 2009; UA060.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001395 - Australian Patent No. 2,007,217,819 - US Patent Nos. 8,460,879; 8,460,878; 8,492,098 - Japanese Patent Nos. 4,790,0026; 5,410,464, 2011 -- 2014; UA060.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001483 - US Patent No. 8,338,776, 2012; UA060.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Walt, David - T001554 - US Patent No. 8,189,191, 2012; UA060.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Hyunmin, Yi - T001695 - Korean Patent No. 10-1,171,738, 2012; UA060.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000971 - Canada Patent No. 2,819,705, 2014; UA060.000163; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by the Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration, 2019, accession UA-2019-074.
  - Bachovchin, William - T000971 - US Patent No. 9,044,424 B2, 2015; UA060.000164; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bachovchin, William - T000971 - US Patent No. 9,102,756 B2 - Israel Patent No. 171854 - Canadian Patent No. 2,525,574, 2014 -- 2015; UA060.000165; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001384 - European Union Patent No. 2400976B1 - Mexico Patent No. 312708 - Japan Patent No. 5270369 - US Patent No. 8,933,056 B2 - US Patent No. 9,192,646 B2, 2013 -- 2016; UA060.000166; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001257 - Australian Patent No. 2005217,642, 2004; UA060.000167; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001396 - Canada Patent No. 2,659,747 - European Union Patent No. 2054386 - US Patent No. 8,889,720 B2 - US Patent No. 9,193,708 B2 - US Patent No. 9,511,060 B2 - T001396 - Korea Patent No. 10-1403887, 2014 -- 2016; UA060.000168; 2 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001674 - Japan Patent No. 5925770 - Russia Patent No. 2588133 - China Patent No. ZL201180040873.X - Australia Patent No. 2011270726, 2010 -- 2016; UA060.000169; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001674 - US Patent No. 8,937,063 B2 - US Patent No. 9,212,142 B2, 2015; UA060.000170; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bachovchin, William - T001795 - US Patent No. 9,284,337 B2, 2016; UA060.000171; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bennett, Clay and Chu, An-Hsiang - T001913 - US Patent No. 9,359,394 B2, 2016; UA060.000172; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Bennett, Clay - T001946 - US Patent No. 9,403,862 B2, 2016; UA060.000173; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bennett, Clay - T001972 - US Patent No. 9,422,325 B2, 2016; UA060.000174; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bright, Alfram - T001656 - US Patent No. 9,216,813 B2, 2015; UA060.000175; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Degterev, Alexei - T001634 - US Patent No. 9,040,585 B2, 2015; UA060.000176; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Diefenbach, Thomas - T001364 - US Patent No. 9,017,991 B2, 2015; UA060.000177; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Haydon, Philip - T001697 - US Patent No. 8,785,620 B2, 2014; UA060.000178; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Haydon, Philip - T001835 - US Patent No. 9,163,055 B2, 2015; UA060.000179; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Haydon, Philip - T001697 - US Patent No. 9,227,993 B2, 2016; UA060.000180; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Herman, Ira - T001414 - US Patent No. 8,663,617 B2, 2014; UA060.000181; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Herman, Ira - T001632 - Australia Patent No. 2009320153 - European Union Patent No. 2344174 - US Patent No. 9,416,161 B2, 2016; UA060.000182; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hopewood, Jeffery - T001762- US Patent No. 9,460,884 B2, 2016; UA060.000183; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Jay, Daniel - T001178 - Israel Patent No. 170818 - US Patent No. 9,068,987 B2, 2015 -- 2016; UA060.000184; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Jin, Hyoung-Joon - T001216 - US Patent No. 9,370,579 B2, 2016; UA060.000185; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 24)